allego.com 2019-05-02

# Privacy Policy | Allego

## **Version June 2018**

This privacy policy discloses the privacy practices for Allego, Inc. This privacy policy applies to information collected by this web site and all Allego family of products across all devices. It will notify you of the following:

  * What personally identifiable information is collected from you, how it is used and with whom it may be shared.
  * What choices are available to you regarding the use of your data.
  * The security procedures in place to protect the misuse of your information.
  * How you can correct any inaccuracies in the information.

### **Information Collection, Use, and Sharing**

We distinguish between information that we collect directly from users of this web site and information submitted to the Allego family of products by its authorize users.

Information collected directly from this web site

We are the sole owners of the information collected directly from users of this website (for example, from individuals who submit requests to receive information about our products and give us their basic contact information for that purpose). We only have access to/collect information that you voluntarily give us via email or other direct contact from you. We will not sell or rent this information to anyone.   We will use your information to respond to you, regarding the reason you contacted us. We will not share your information with any third party outside of our organization, other than as necessary to fulfill your request, for example, to confirm a registration. Unless you ask us not to, we may contact you via email in the future to tell you about industry insights, new products or services, or changes to this privacy policy.

When we receive information directly from visitors to this web site who are citizens or residents of the European Union, that information is likely to include “personal data,” as regulated by the European Union’s General Data Protection Regulation (“GDPR”). As the recipient of this information (generally just contact information), Allego is a data “controller” under the GDPR.  As such, Allego will use that information only for the limited purpose of providing information about our products and services until the person who submitted the information no longer wishes that to occur, and anyone who submits personal data to this web site consents to our use of that data for those purposes. As mandated by the GDPR, we will respond to your requests to delete, correct, transfer, provide information about and otherwise manage the data you have submitted to this web site.  You may opt out of any future contacts from us at any time. We provide these rights to anyone who submits information to our web site, whether or not he or she is a citizen or resident of the European Union, To request any of those services, please contact us at privacy@allego.com. 

Information submitted to the Allego family of products by its authorize users

If you are using one of our products, you have received authorization to do so from your employer (or if you are not an employee, from a business to which you provide services in another capacity).  In this case, Allego has entered into a contract with the business you work for, and that contract will govern how we handle any information that you submit to our product on behalf of the business you work for.  Under the GDPR, Allego is the data “processor” of this information, and the business you work for is the data controller. Allego complies with its agreements with data controllers, which generally give the data controllers full decision-making power regarding the collection, storage, processing, modification, deletion, and transfer of any information submitted to our products.  

### **Security**

We take precautions to protect your information. When you submit sensitive information via the website, your information is protected both online and offline. Wherever we collect sensitive information, that information is encrypted and transmitted to us in a secure way.

While we use encryption to protect sensitive information transmitted online, we also protect your information offline. Only employees who need the information to perform a specific job (for example, billing or customer service) are granted access to personally identifiable information. The computers/servers in which we store personally identifiable information are kept in a secure environment.

### **Updates**  

Our Privacy Policy may change from time to time and all updates will be posted on this page.

If you feel that we are not abiding by this privacy policy, you should contact us immediately at privacy@allego.com.
